[Music]
[音乐]
hello thank you for coming here this
你好，谢谢你来到这里
morning my name is Joe Darcy I work in
早上我叫乔·达西，我在这里工作
Oracle's Java platform group and I'll be
Oracle的Java平台小组，我将成为
speaking today about JDK 9 language
今天谈到JDK 9语言
tooling and library features there's a
工具和库功能有一个
lot of material in the talk today if we
如果我们今天在谈话中有很多材料
don't have time for questions at the end
最后没有时间提问
you can tweet your questions to the
您可以将您的问题发布到
hashtag here shown on the first slide
标签显示在第一张幻灯片上
I'll also be tweeting a link to PDF of
我还将在Twitter上发布以下内容的PDF链接：
the slides after the talk this is a very
谈话后的幻灯片，这是一个非常
important slide from Oracle's legal team
Oracle法律团队的重要幻灯片
they want you to know to not trust very
他们想让你知道不要非常信任
much what I have to say here today they
今天我在这里不得不说很多
call this the safe harbor statement
将此称为安全港声明
however is one developer to another if
但是如果一个开发者是另一个
you're interested in safe harbors there
您对那里的安全港感兴趣
are many other safe harbors in the area
该地区还有许多其他安全港
we could talk about so I'm happy to
我们可以谈谈，所以我很高兴
share some tips on those after the talk
在演讲后分享一些提示
quick survey of the audience of which
快速调查其中的受众
JDK trains you're using in production
JDK培训您在生产中使用的培训
JDK 9 early access with jigsaw cutting
JDK 9拼图切割的早期访问
in jigsaw any hands there well about the
在拼图中，关于
other JDK 9 early access build some
其他JDK 9早期访问版本
people downloaded them that's good
人们下载了它们，很好
perhaps a few more you will download
也许还会下载更多
this after the talk dedicate so most of
谈话结束后，这大部分
the audience using JDK 8 it's very good
使用JDK 8的观众非常好
from if you is back people still on 7
如果你回来了，人们仍然在7
maybe 1/4 the audience for 7 still
也许1/4的观众仍然是7
stalled release 6 a few more hands there
停滞释放6多了几手
and admit it it's ok we're all friends
并承认没关系，我们都是朋友
here
这里
KD K 5 or earlier I a few few very
KD K 5或更早的版本
people do admit well there are many new
人们确实承认有很多新
features are since then perhaps so
从那时起也许就是这样
you'll be able to get motivated to
您将有动力去
upgrade by the end of the talk quick
谈话快结束时升级
overview of what's in JDK 9 JD canines
JDK 9 JD犬齿概述
been in development for a number of
已经开发了许多
years and the ship date the early for
年和船期早于
the general availability is coming up in
一般可用性即将出现
a few months in July as I mentioned
正如我提到的，在七月的几个月
there are early access binaries for two
有两个的早期访问二进制文件
lines of development both the main line
发展线既是主线
one and one with jigsaw features that's
一个和一个具有拼图功能的
a little more cutting edge JDK nines
先进的JDK九点
being developed under the auspices of
在...的主持下发展
open JDK so there's a project for that
打开JDK，因此有一个项目
their various mailing lists you
他们的各种邮件列表
the source code if you're interested
源代码（如果您有兴趣）
there's also various adoption groups one
还有各种各样的收养小组
of the initiatives we expanded for JDK 9
我们为JDK 9扩展的计划中的一些
was to reach out to various open source
是为了接触各种开源
projects to have the muse of JDK 9 early
项目尽早使用JDK 9
access builds along the way so we can
访问方式一路走来，我们可以
get more feedback about what's working
获得有关工作原理的更多反馈
well and what's working less well
好，什么工作不好
throughout the rest of the talk I'll be
在接下来的演讲中，我将
using the term Jeff these are JDK
使用术语Jeff这些是JDK
enhancement proposals and they're a
增强建议，它们是
process we use to manage feature work
我们用于管理要素工作的过程
now in the JDK and Duke needs you yes
现在在JDK和Duke中需要您
you to download these early access
您下载这些抢先体验
builds try them out in your CI systems
在您的CI系统中进行尝试
and let us know what's working what's
让我们知道什么在起作用
not we are fairly far along in the cycle
不是我们在周期中走得很远
for JDK 9 we're one of the ramp down
对于JDK 9，我们是其中之一
phases but there's still time to send us
阶段，但仍有时间发送给我们
some feedback and let us know how it's
一些反馈，让我们知道如何
going the capsule summary of JDK 9 the
关于JDK 9的总结
largest feature in JDK 9 is modularity
JDK 9的最大功能是模块化
this has been in progress for a number
这已经进行了许多
of years under project jigsaw and
项目拼图的年限和
modules bundled together multiple
多个模块捆绑在一起
packages and offer a stronger
包装并提供更强大的
encapsulation than jar files earlier
比jar文件更早的封装
this week there have already been a
这周已经有一个
number of DevOps sessions about
关于的DevOps会话数
modularity which you may have already
您可能已经拥有的模块化
seen this is a very large change it's a
看到这是一个很大的变化，这是一个
language change to the in a larger
语言转换成更大的
change of the platform there's a new
平台的变化有一个新的
kind of Java file a module info file
一种Java文件模块信息文件
that allows the dependencies between
允许之间的依赖
modules to be declared Java C compiles
声明为Java C的模块编译
those files then at runtime the Java
这些文件，然后在运行时Java
commands also been updated to enforce
命令也已更新以强制执行
the same kind of dependency restrictions
相同的依赖项限制
declared in module info files there's
在模块信息文件中声明有
various other supporting changes as well
其他各种支持更改
such as in Co reflection and the
例如在Co反射和
language model API as a large language
语言模型API作为一种大语言
change it did affect many parts of the
变化确实影响了
platform project lambda and JDK 8 was
平台项目lambda和JDK 8是
also a large language change however the
语言变化也很大
modularity changes in JDK 9 are somewhat
JDK 9中的模块性变化有些
bigger in the sense that they addressed
他们解决的意义更大
the programming model more fundamentally
更根本地编程模型
with modules you're able to program in
使用您可以编程的模块
the large at a different granularity so
大的以不同的粒度
you have different questions to consider
你有不同的问题要考虑
when you're designing your application
在设计应用程序时
library in terms of what the module
关于什么模块的库
boundaries are not just what set of
边界不仅是什么
types you might have there are their JDK
您可能拥有的JDK类型
9 related talks at devoxx there are some
在devoxx的9个相关讲座中有一些
early week my colleague
一周前我的同事
l gave a talk yesterday about the sharp
我昨天讲了关于
edges of JDK 9 I like to think of this
JDK 9的优势，我想这个
talk today is covering not only the
今天的谈话不仅涵盖了
sharp edges but also some of the rounded
锋利的边缘，但也有一些倒圆角
corners personally I prefer the classic
我个人比较喜欢经典
og profile as shown here there are a
og配置文件，如此处所示，有一个
number of other data k9 related talks
与k9相关的其他数据的讨论次数
later today as well I'll just highlight
今天晚些时候，我也将重点介绍
two of them now
现在两个
Trisha key later this morning is going
特里莎（Trisha）钥匙今天早上要去
to be talking about tooling support in
在谈论工具支持
IntelliJ for JDK 9 and this afternoon
IntelliJ for JDK 9和今天下午
Minaj plot is also going to be talking
Minaj剧情也将在谈论
about the Eclipse support for JDK 9 with
关于Eclipse对JDK 9的支持
modern development of course it's not
当然不是现代发展
just about the support from language
只是语言的支持
feature that ships in the JDK we also
JDK中附带的功能
want to have good support in tools such
希望在诸如此类的工具中获得良好的支持
as iges outline for the rest of the talk
正如艾格斯在接下来的演讲中概述的那样
I'll give a brief discussion of the
我将简要讨论
stewardship philosophy we use in the
我们在
Java platform group toward evolving Java
Java平台组朝着不断发展的Java迈进
just give some sense of the size of JDK
只是对JDK的大小有所了解
9 JD 9 is a very large release in the
9 JD 9是
terms of number of bug fixes this is a
错误修复数量，这是一个
graph comparing the JDK 9 bug fixes per
比较每个JDK 9错误修复的图形
build to JDK 8 and we've had a higher
建立到JDK 8，我们有一个更高的
fix rate 9 and the release has gone on
修复率9，发布继续进行
for longer we're starting to level off
更长的时间，我们开始趋于平稳
now this is a from a week or two ago so
现在这是一两个星期前的
there are a lot of good good changes in
有很多好的变化
JDK 9 those changes span a number of
JDK 9这些更改跨越了许多
areas there's tooling improvements
在工具方面有所改进
language changes and library updates
语言更改和库更新
sometimes the features are well
有时候功能很好
delineating into these buckets sometimes
有时划出这些水桶
they cross over so this is just a rough
他们越过所以这只是一个粗糙
outline of the rest of talk and if we
其余谈话的大纲，如果我们
have some time at the end I'll take
最后我会花一些时间
questions and answers stewardship the
问答管理
approach we use to stewardship for Java
我们用来管理Java的方法
is not the same approach that we do say
与我们所说的方法不同
by Denethor in the Lord of the Rings
戴涅索在《指环王》中
films we have a more benign in the
电影，我们在
supporter view of stewardship for Java
Java管理的支持者视图
under the last seven years under Oracle
在甲骨文的最近七年
there's been a consistent top priority
有一个始终如一的首要任务
for the Java platform group which is to
对于Java平台组
keep Java vibrant part of keeping Java
保持Java充满活力是保持Java的一部分
vibrant is keeping things that work
朝气蓬勃的东西正在保持工作
today working tomorrow and that brings
今天工作明天
us to a discussion of compatibility and
我们来讨论兼容性和
the general evolution policy we use for
我们使用的一般进化政策
Java and that general evolution Paul
Java与一般进化论Paul
the for compatibility is we don't want
为了兼容性，我们不想要
to break binary compatibility as
破坏二进制兼容性为
defining the Java language specification
定义Java语言规范
and what that means is we want to keep
那意味着我们要保持
programs that link today linking
今天链接的程序
tomorrow we want to avoid introducing
明天我们要避免介绍
source incompatibilities and we want to
源不兼容，我们希望
manage behavioral compatibilities so
管理行为兼容性
this extends to language evolution as
这扩展到语言进化
well it means that we want to continue
好吧，这意味着我们要继续
to recognize old class files even all
识别所有旧文件
the way back to those 1440 5.3 class
回到那些1440 5.3班级的方式
files from jdk 102 we want to limit the
来自jdk 102的文件，我们希望限制
cases where currently legal code stops
当前法律法规停止的情况
compiling and we want to avoid a change
编译，我们希望避免更改
in code generation that introduced
在引入的代码生成中
behavioral change surprisingly and we
行为改变令人惊讶，我们
don't just want to keep everything the
不只是想保留一切
same because then there'd be no progress
一样，因为那样就没有进展
so there is a balancing act between
因此，在
stability in progress with the
进行中的稳定性
recognition that there is a lot of value
认识到有很多价值
in good compatibility and keeping things
保持良好的兼容性并保持良好状态
working so we've talked about there's
工作，所以我们谈到了
three dimensions of compatibility so
兼容性的三个方面
we're spying and behavioral so we could
我们从事间谍活动和行为举止，因此我们可以
view those as defining a little vector
认为那些定义了一个小向量
space like you might might recall from a
您可能会想起的空间
physics class and we have different
物理课，我们有不同
policies about compatibility for the
有关兼容性的政策
different kinds of releases we have so
我们有不同的发行版本
for instance if we have the quarterly
例如，如果我们有季度报告
security updates those have a very small
安全更新的那些很小
region where they can make incompatible
他们可能使之不兼容的区域
changes so you recognize by this box
变化，因此您可以通过此框识别
here we want to have some behavioral
在这里我们想要一些行为
change after all if there's some bad
毕竟如果有一些不好的地方就改变
code that we want to stop working we
我们想要停止工作的代码
want that to stop working so that would
希望那停止工作，这样
be incompatible for an X point for
对于X点不兼容
example and maybe there's a little bit
例子，也许有一点
of source coding ability we allow for a
源编码能力，我们允许
larger update release say 8u 20 or au 40
较大的更新版本，例如8u 20或au 40
there's more fixes going in more
还有更多的修复程序
features so we'd have a larger region we
功能，所以我们会有更大的区域
allow there but in both cases we stay in
允许在那里，但在两种情况下，我们都留在
the source behavior plain meaning
源行为朴素的意义
there's no binary compatibility change
没有二进制兼容性更改
that we allow because we want people to
之所以允许，是因为我们希望人们
be able to easily update to the update
能够轻松更新到更新
releases without having to worry about
发布而不必担心
their program stopping to link the
他们的程序停止链接
situation's a little different for
情况有些不同
platform releases like JDK 8 GA and now
平台版本，例如JDK 8 GA和现在
especially JDK 9 we have a larger
特别是JDK 9，我们有一个更大的
ability region to play with more
玩更多的能力区域
behavioral change more source code
行为改变更多源代码
change and with enough justification
变化并有充分的理由
even some binary and compatible changes
甚至一些二进制和兼容的更改
and we'll see one or two examples of
我们将看到一个或两个例子
that later in the talk so a good example
在谈话的后面，这是一个很好的例子
to help illustrate the different kinds
帮助说明不同的种类
of behavioral change policy we can look
我们可以看一下行为改变政策
at the specification of hash set that
在哈希集的规范中
iterator it says here you get back an
迭代器说，这里你回来了
iterator and the elements are returned
迭代器和元素被返回
in no particular order that means if
没有特定顺序意味着
your program relies on the order your
您的程序取决于您的订单
program is kind of bugging it also means
程序有点bug，也意味着
that we are allowed by the specification
规范允许的
to change the order but that doesn't
更改顺序，但这并没有
mean we always change it so what is the
意味着我们总是会更改它，那么什么是
compatibility impact if we did change
如果我们进行了更改，将对兼容性产生影响
the hash that iteration order well first
迭代顺序良好的哈希
its binary compatible the set of methods
它的二进制兼容方法集
isn't changing so there's no concern
没有改变，所以不用担心
there it's also source compatible for
那里也有源兼容
the same reason it's not going to change
同样的原因，它不会改变
how your code compiles however it is
您的代码如何编译
this third kind of change it is a
这第三种变化是
behavioral change and we know people can
行为改变，我们知道人们可以
in do in facility lie on the iteration
设施中的实际情况取决于迭代
order we even have some examples of this
为了我们甚至有一些这样的例子
in our own jdk code base that bite us
在我们自己的jdk代码库中
now again therefore this kind of change
现在又是这种变化
changing casts that iteration order
改变演员的迭代顺序
would generally be out of bounds for an
通常会超出范围
update release but it would be something
更新版本，但这将是
we could do and have done in a platform
我们可以在一个平台上做，也可以做
release and we do this today to take
发布，我们今天就这样做
advantage of better hash algorithms that
更好的哈希算法的优势
are developed over time so if you want
随着时间的推移发展，所以如果你想
to learn more about this for a
进一步了解这一点
particular release you can look at the
特定版本，您可以查看
release notes and compatibility guides
发行说明和兼容性指南
they do use this source by new
他们确实使用新的来源
behavioral classification there's this
行为分类
document was produced along those lines
文件是按照这些思路制作的
for JDK 8 and within the next few months
适用于JDK 8，并在接下来的几个月内
there'll also be a similar guide
也会有类似的指南
produced for JDK 9 so how is data canine
为JDK 9生产的，数据犬如何
different as I mentioned before it is
正如我之前提到的不同
allowing a larger range to make
允许更大范围
incompatible changes and this is to
不兼容的更改，这是为了
further the long term evolution of the
进一步的长期发展
platform there are some things we
平台上有些事情我们
haven't done before so for instance if
以前没有这样做过，例如，如果
you would lie down the existence of our
你会躺下我们的存在
char for some reason that file is no
char由于某种原因文件不存在
longer there one of the cases where we
在这种情况下，更长的时间之一
broke binary compatibility involved some
破坏了二进制兼容性，涉及到一些
unfortunate use of the beans API in
不幸的是在
far-flung parts of platform J
J平台的远侧部分
java.util java.util jar that's part of
属于java.util的java.util jar
the base knowledge we want to be able to
我们希望能够掌握的基础知识
keep the base module nice and small but
保持基本模块的美观和小巧，但
in a few cases it used part of the beans
在某些情况下，它使用了部分豆子
API which pulled in all the desktop
引入所有桌面的API
module so we didn't want to have the
模块，所以我们不想拥有
base model to include all this hop as
基本模型，将所有跃点都包括在内
well so the solution to this was first
好吧，这是第一个解决方案
to deprecate these methods in eight with
用八种方法淘汰这些方法
a warning they'd be removed in nine and
警告，他们将在九点之内被删除，
now we've gone through and removed them
现在我们已经完成并删除了它们
a nine so that is a binary incompatible
一个九，所以是二进制不兼容
change if you relied on these methods
如果您依赖这些方法，请更改
they're not there anymore however we
他们不在那里了，但是我们
thought it was important enough to have
认为拥有足够重要
a better bod pob module D competition to
更好的bod pob模块D竞争
the platform to make that change and if
进行更改的平台，如果
you're interested in defecation matters
您对排便感兴趣
we'll be saying more about that later in
我们稍后会讲更多
the talk and I encourage you to follow
演讲，我鼓励您关注
doctor deprecated er who takes care of a
不赞成使用er的医生
delicate Pat ability on Java deprecation
Java弃用的微妙Pat功能
on twitter onto some of the tooling
在推特上介绍一些工具
improvements first up is J shell in the
改进首先是J shell
list community there's been a long
列表社区已经有很长一段时间了
tradition of providing a read evaluate
提供阅读评估的传统
print loop called the repple as a way of
打印循环称为repple作为一种方式
interacting with the language if you
如果您与语言互动
coming from the Ruby or Python community
来自Ruby或Python社区
you have similar functionality there and
你在那里有类似的功能，
on the VM side if you work with Scala a
在VM端，如果您使用Scala a
ruby enclosure there's also this kind of
红宝石外壳，也有这种
repple you're used to so what about Java
reprep你已经习惯了，那么Java呢？
what wouldn't a repple be nice for Java
对于Java来说，什么都不是很好
as well we thought so too and that led
我们也这么认为，导致
to the JDK 9 project of adding J shell
到添加J shell的JDK 9项目
and I'll give a quick teaser demo of
我将快速演示一下
that here and that is not the window I
在这里，那不是窗户
want
想
okay so this is Jay shells new command
好的，这是Jay shell的新命令
in the JDK this is JDK installed from a
在JDK中，这是从
recent did here on early access so we'll
最近在这里进行了早期访问，所以我们将
wait for that to start up here so what's
等待它开始在这里，那是什么
the first program you write in any
您在任何情况下编写的第一个程序
language hello world so we can excuse me
语言你好世界，所以我们可以原谅我
type down here now we see it comes back
现在在这里键入，我们看到它回来了
right away
马上
so we executed a first Jake shell
所以我们执行了第一个Jake Shell
program so this is just actually new
程序，所以这实际上是新的
string back to us but you notice we
回到我们身边，但你注意到我们
didn't have to say public static void
不必说公共静态无效
main string args so forth so there's
主字符串参数等等，所以
much less ceremony to get started here
更少的仪式开始
we can just start playing around we can
我们可以开始玩耍，我们可以
also say declare variables so let's say
也说声明变量，所以说
we want to have a double variable tau
我们想要一个双变量tau
and we want that to be equal to two
我们希望那等于二
times pi so we know there's a pi
圆周率，所以我们知道有圆周率
constant to find in the math class we
在数学课上找到的常数
can tap complete for math here and then
可以在此处点击完成数学，然后
we know that pi constants there so that
我们知道pi常数在那里
autocompletes and then we get that back
自动完成，然后我们取回
to us of course we don't want just
对我们来说，我们当然不只是
fields we also want methods so let's say
我们也需要方法的字段，所以说
we want to find a method square that
我们想找到一个方法平方
takes a double and squares it
取双并平方
now this methods in our environment so
现在这种方法在我们的环境中
we can complete on that and we can
我们可以做到这一点，我们可以
square a towel and we get back something
摆一条毛巾，我们得到一些东西
that's about the right size so that's
大小合适，所以
good
好
there's also command line editing so if
还有命令行编辑，所以如果
we want to say take the square of the
我们想说的是
sign of the value and add it to the
值的符号并将其添加到
square of the cosign we should get
我们应该得到的符号的平方
something close to one and that is
接近一个的东西就是
indeed what we get so going back to the
的确，我们得到的回溯到
slides so as I mentioned there's less
幻灯片，就像我提到的那样
ceremony for students getting started
学生入门仪式
and Java you don't have to worry about
和Java，您不必担心
what public static void mean on the
公共静态无效对
first day but this isn't a feature just
第一天，但​​这不只是功能
for people new to Java it's also a
对于Java新手来说，
useful tool for experienced developers
经验丰富的开发人员的有用工具
this might be a good way for example to
例如，这可能是一个好方法
start experimenting with those new and
开始尝试那些新的和
nine JDK nine library features the
九个JDK九个库的功能
implementation of JCL leverages many
JCL的实现利用了许多
existing JDK technologies and the lead
现有的JDK技术和领先者
engineer for Jade shell my colleague
我的同事Jade Shell的工程师
Robert field will be giving a talk about
罗伯特·菲尔德将发表演讲
this later today if you're interested to
今天晚些时候，如果您有兴趣
hear a lot more about it next up we'll
接下来，我们会听到更多的信息
talk about Java doc for many years Java
谈论Java多年的Java文档
doc output was done to the 4.01 HTML
doc输出已完成到4.01 HTML
standard a few years ago there's a new
几年前的标准
HTML standard html5 so now you can opt
HTML标准html5，因此您现在可以选择
in your Java doc output to be html5
在您的Java文档输出中为html5
instead of HTML 401 although we don't
而不是HTML 401，尽管我们没有
have any videos enabled by default how
默认情况下启用了任何视频
many people have used a doc length from
许多人使用了
JDK 8 no hands well this if you're
JDK 8不好用，如果您
concerned about the semantic and
关注语义和
syntactic correctness of your Java doc
Java文档的语法正确性
you can now check that using dockland
您现在可以使用码头区进行检查
either as part of Java C or as part of
作为Java C的一部分或作为
the Java doc command one of the changes
Java doc命令的更改之一
to document one of the improvements we
记录我们的一项改进
added in JDK 9 was packaged filtering so
JDK 9中添加的内容已打包过滤，因此
for instance in the JDK build we only
例如在JDK构建中，我们仅
dock
码头
the Java and Java ex packages and don't
Java和Java ex软件包，不要
bother worrying about the Javadoc
担心Javadoc
correctness to the same degree for the
相同程度的正确性
implementation classes say in dedicated
实施类专门讲
star or some not star the Java doc
给Java文档加星标或不加星标
checks you can enable or disable these
检查您是否可以启用或禁用这些
individually they range from things from
个别地，它们的范围从
syntactic well formulas of the HTML to
HTML的语法良好公式
semantics checks to make sure your FC
语义检查以确保您的FC
and link tags have valid targets if you
和链接标记具有有效的目标，如果您
write doclets we've updated the doclet
编写doclet我们已经更新了doclet
api to have a better foundation the old
api有更好的基础
doclet api was done very early in the
doclet api是在
Java platform I think it's fair to say
我认为Java平台很公平
it doesn't it didn't follow what are now
不是不是没有遵循现在
considered best practices for API design
被认为是API设计的最佳实践
and we were able to re-implement this on
并且我们能够重新实现
a more recent language model and reuse
更新的语言模型和重用
that from another part of the platform
来自平台另一部分的
another feature we added to Java doc is
我们添加到Java文档的另一个功能是
a Java doc search box and we'll have
一个Java文档搜索框，我们将拥有
another quick demo of that okay so this
另一个好的快速演示，所以这
is the Java doc output for a recent JDK
是最新JDK的Java文档输出
9 build you'll notice the frames view is
9版本您会注意到框架视图是
not no longer the default with those
不再是那些的默认值
three panels if you still like that you
三个面板，如果您仍然喜欢的话
can get it from over here four frames
可以从这里得到四个帧
and now in the upper right hand corner
现在在右上角
there's a search box so let's say we
有一个搜索框，所以我们说
want to search for math we see here the
想搜索数学，我们在这里看到
search returns results in different
搜索返回不同的结果
areas it searches over the names of
它搜索的区域名称
packages the names of types in the
将类型名称打包
signatures of fields and methods and we
字段和方法的签名，我们
see all all of those showing up here in
看到所有出现在这里的人
the search output and then you can just
搜索输出，然后您就可以
select to go directly there we've added
选择直接去那里，我们添加了
modules in JDK 9 so this also works over
JDK 9中的模块，因此这也可以解决
modules for instance if we look for the
例如，如果我们寻找
base module it shows that as a module
基本模块显示为一个模块
result and we can also look over the
结果，我们还可以查看
packages in that module we usually lose
该模块中的软件包，我们通常会丢失
camelcase naming convention in Java and
Java和Java中的camelcase命名约定
sometimes the method names are kind of
有时方法名称有点
long so let's say we wanted to find out
很久以来，我们想找出答案
the Javadoc for equals ignore case we
Javadoc for equals忽略大小写
could type that whole thing out but
可以把整个东西都打出来
that'd be a little inconvenient so we
这有点不方便，所以我们
can use cam
可以使用凸轮
okay search instead so we go equal and
好吧，搜索，所以我们去平等，
then ID for ignore and now we can select
然后是ID即可忽略，现在我们可以选择
which of the two methods we want there
我们想要那里两种方法中的哪一种
so it's a nice quick way to look up
所以这是一种很好的快速查找方法
information in Javadoc now so you'll
Javadoc中的信息，现在您可以
less often you'll be tempted to use the
较少地，您会倾向于使用
search engines to find things in Javadoc
搜索引擎来查找Javadoc中的内容
you can just use Javadoc itself the
您可以只使用Javadoc本身
search feature is implemented side in
搜索功能在侧面实现
JavaScript so it's runnable locally you
JavaScript，因此您可以在本地运行
don't need to have a server to do this
不需要服务器即可执行此操作
as I mentioned it indexes over all sorts
正如我提到的那样，它可以对各种索引进行索引
of names and signatures present in the
存在的名称和签名
Javadoc from type names to the module
Javadoc从类型名称到模块
names you can also using a new tag to
您也可以使用新标签来命名
find your own index terms that will show
找到您自己的索引字词，以显示
up in the search the next two features
搜索以下两个功能
I'll talk about concerning the
我将谈论有关
transitioning from one JDK release to
从一个JDK版本过渡到
another multi release jar files and the
另一个多版本的jar文件和
Java C dash dash release flag so first
Java C破折号释放标志，所以先
will be about cross compiling with this
将与此交叉编译
new - gasps release flag so Java sees
新-喘息释放标志，以便Java看到
along been across compiler you've been
一直跨编译器，您一直
able to use Java C to compile from the
能够使用Java C从
current J today back to older ones I've
今天的J回到我以前的
written a blog entry about how to do
写了一篇关于如何做的博客文章
this it's also in the Java C man page
这也在Java C手册页中
and there are three things you have to
还有三件事
set for your Java C command to make this
为您的Java C命令设置此功能
work properly you have to set the source
工作正常，您必须设置源
version you're using you have to set the
您使用的版本必须设置
target version and finally you have to
目标版本，最后您必须
set the bloop class path to the boot
将bloop类路径设置为引导
class path through the earlier JDK
早期JDK的类路径
release related to this we've changed
与此相关的版本已更改
the policy about how many source and
关于有多少来源和
target versions we support instead of
我们支持的目标版本，而不是
going all the way back to the beginning
一直回到起点
we now have a version of one plus three
我们现在有一个一加三的版本
back
背部
we started this in JDK 8 so if a JDK 9
我们是从JDK 8开始的，所以如果是JDK 9
that means for source and target we
这意味着对于源和目标，我们
support nine eight seven and six however
支持九八七七
six is deprecated and a warning is
已弃用六个，警告为
issued when we use it so following this
当我们使用它时发出
policy and JDK 10 the six option isn't
策略和JDK 10的六个选项不是
supported anymore but used to have ten
支持了，但过去有十个
nine eight and seven and seven is
九八，七，七是
deprecated and so on so why do you need
弃用等等，为什么您需要
to set the boot class path well let's
设置好引导类路径，让我们
take an example here of JK Library in
在这里以JK库为例
JDK version 10 there's one method foo
JDK版本10中只有一种方法foo
that takes a double Letton let's say in
需要两倍的Letton来说
JT
日本电信
plus one an overload for foods out of
再加上一个超载的食物
the takes an INT and let's assume that
需要一个INT，让我们假设
these are semantically equivalent but
这些在语义上是等效的，但是
it's just a fast pass for in stove it it
这只是炉子的快速通行证
would follow all the usual behavioral
会遵循所有通常的行为
the compatibility rules we care about so
我们关心的兼容性规则
this is a perfectly reasonable library
这是一个非常合理的图书馆
change for the JDK now let's have our
现在更改JDK
client library that calls two so if we
客户端库调用两个，所以如果我们
take the client library here and compile
将客户端库放在这里并进行编译
it against JDK n plus one what does the
它针对JDK n加一
call of foo mean so Fouchier takes an
foo的调用意味着Fouchier需要一个
integer argument so then if we go over
整数参数，所以如果我们过去
to JDK n plus one which of the two foo
到JDK n加两个foo中的哪一个
methods is going to get put into the
方法将被投入
class file this is going to be the
类文件，这将是
method that takes a double of the method
方法是方法的两倍
that takes an int it's going to be the
这需要一个int，它将是
method that takes in it right that's
正确的方法就是
about the most specific method that's
关于最具体的方法
what the spec says to have let's say we
规范说的是什么，假设我们
take that class file even if it has the
即使该类文件具有
class Hall version for the older JDK n
旧版JDK的class Hall版本
version now we run it against JDK n
版本，现在我们针对JDK运行它
what's going to happen we're going to
将会发生什么，我们将要
get an error or something like this at
出现错误或类似的东西
runtime no such method error now if we
如果我们现在运行时没有这样的方法错误
decode what the error message says here
解码错误消息在这里说什么
it basically says I'm looking for a
它基本上说我正在寻找一个
method foo in the in the library class
库类中的foo方法
that takes an integer that's what the
它需要一个整数，即
eye and parentheses means and of course
眼睛和括号意味着，当然
in JDK n there is no such method because
在JDK n中没有这样的方法，因为
we only have the method foo that takes a
我们只有方法foo需要一个
double now to avoid this sort of
现在加倍以避免这种情况
mismatch this is why you need to use the
不匹配，这就是为什么您需要使用
boob class path from the older version
旧版本的boob类路径
when you're cross compiling so we've
当您交叉编译时，我们
known about this problem for a while and
知道这个问题一段时间
people could keep reporting bugs about
人们可以不断报告有关的错误
it in food alright well we'll provide
好吧，我们会提供食物
some help in JDK 7 if you use a the
如果您使用的是JDK 7中的一些帮助
older source of targets and you don't
目标的旧来源，而您没有
set the booth class path will issue a
设置展位的班级路径将发出
warning you can suppress the warning if
警告您可以取消警告，如果
you want so that's fine we thought that
你想要所以很好，我们认为
would prevent people from running across
会阻止人们跑来跑去
this problem but we were little too
这个问题，但我们也很少
optimistic about that we still had bugs
乐观地说我们仍然有错误
coming in about this so we thought about
进来这个，所以我们想到了
it some more in for jdk 9 we thought you
还有更多关于jdk 9的内容，我们认为您
know what we know what people want to do
知道我们知道人们想做什么
here they just want to cross compile to
在这里，他们只是想交叉编译为
the older version so why don't we
旧版本，所以我们为什么不
provide that functionality directly
直接提供该功能
instead of having people to approximate
而不是让人们去近似
themselves
他们自己
so that's exactly what we did with the -
所以这正是我们对-
- release and option that's semantically
-语义上的发布和选项
equivalent to specifying the source
等同于指定来源
target in boot class path and now that
目标在启动类路径中，现在
boot class path information is provided
提供了引导类路径信息
to Java C stored in the compressed form
以Java C压缩格式存储
as a additional bonus the information
作为额外的奖励信息
available and release release - after
可用并发布版本-之后
Lisa and only the api's we think you
丽莎和只有api的我们认为您
should be calling so those are the Java
应该打电话，所以那些是Java
SE e api's and the exported api's of the
SE e api和导出的api
jdk so things like the those tempting
jdk这样的东西很诱人
Son Nhut star api's are not covered in
Son Nhut星型api不在以下内容中
now and you for - after issue have the
现在和你-问题后
same set of options as for source and
与来源和
target so if you advantages here if you
目标，如果你在这里优势，如果你
were setting the boot class path
正在设置引导类路径
previously you don't have to worry about
以前您不必担心
managing that artifact anymore where do
不再管理该工件
you get the boot class pass from some
你从一些引导类传递
people use the maven plugin animal
人们使用Maven插件动物
sniffer and he will use that plugin one
嗅探器，他将使用该插件之一
or two hands so that did the same sort
或两只手，做同样的事情
of checking that shouldn't be as
检查不应该
necessary anymore because it's built
不再需要，因为它是内置的
right onto Java say write write in Java
直接上Java说用Java写
C it also means that if you using Java C
C也意味着如果您使用Java C
from manure releases you can take
可以从粪便中释放
advantage of bug fixes and some possible
错误修复的优势和一些可能的方法
for performance improvements that might
可能会提高性能
have gone on since the earlier jdk
从早期的jdk开始
another feature we've add to help each
我们添加的另一个功能可以帮助每个人
transition to newer jdk is multi release
过渡到较新的jdk是多版本
jar files so if you have a library
jar文件，所以如果您有一个库
application it would be inconvenient to
应用它会给您带来不便
have to distribute a jar file one for
必须分发一个jar文件
jdk n and another Ek Tha n plus one so
jdk n和另一个Ek Tha n加一个
people instead will distribute a single
人们会分配一个
jar file you compile against the oldest
针对最旧的jar文件进行编译
jdk they want to run on that has a few
他们要在上面运行的jdk有一些
consequences it does slow down the
结果确实减慢了
adoption and new features because it's
采用和新功能，因为它是
awkward to use the features in the new
尴尬地使用新功能
or jdk sometimes you can get around that
或jdk有时您可以解决
using reflection but that's slow and
使用反射，但这很慢，
somewhat awkward and the modularity
有点尴尬和模块化
features in jdk 9 make some of those you
jdk 9的功能使其中一些功能
shouldn't be using them api is harder to
不应该使用它们api更难
access so this wouldn't work quite as
访问，所以这将无法正常工作
well so you're trying to rewrite it now
好，所以您现在要重写它
is multi release draw files the idea is
是多版本绘图文件的想法是
pretty simple there's a common shared
很简单，有一个共同的共享
area across all versions but then under
所有版本的区域，然后在
the meta in area there are jdk platform
该区域中的meta有jdk平台
specific
具体
overrides you could have a little ride
覆盖您可能会骑一会儿
source eight nine and ten that take
源八九十
advantage of nine and ten specific
九点和十点的优势
functionality the multi release jar
多功能释放罐的功能
files are created using new options to
使用新选项创建文件
the jar command and the parts of the
jar命令和部分
platform which consume jar files of the
平台使用的jar文件
jar API the Java the Java command in
jar API Java Java命令
Java C have been updated to be multi
Java C已更新为多
release aware next I'll talk about some
接下来我会讲一些释放
of the language changes non modularity
语言的变化非模块化
language changes that have gone into JDK
JDK中已进行的语言更改
9 the first of those would be in milling
9首先是铣削
project coin so the term milling a coin
投射硬币，因此术语“碾磨硬币”
refers to putting those little ridges
指把那些小山脊
around the edge of the coin as shown the
如图所示，围绕硬币的边缘
silver dollars here the motivation for
银币在这里的动机
this was when coins were generally made
这是一般制作硬币的时候
of precious metal like silver or gold
贵金属，如银或金
people tend to shave down the edges of
人们倾向于剃光
the coin and then sell that separately
硬币，然后单独出售
kind of a debasing the coin and by
一种贬低硬币和
putting the ridges on the coin it makes
将山脊放在制作的硬币上
it more obvious that that's going on in
更明显的是，
preventing that so in the same idea for
在相同的想法中防止这种情况
milling project coin one you maintain
您维护的铣削项目硬币
the value of the coin features over time
随着时间的推移，硬币特征的价值
by filing off some rust rough edges that
通过去除一些生锈的粗糙边缘
were left at the end of the JDK a seven
在JDK的末尾剩下了七个
as a reminder these are the project coin
提醒一下，这些是项目硬币
features from JDK seven and three of
JDK的第七和第三项功能
them have small updates in JDK 9
他们在JDK 9中有小的更新
these are the updates we'll be talking
这些是我们要谈论的更新
about three of them are for project coin
其中大约三个用于项目硬币
there were some similar situations for
有一些类似的情况
project lambda where they had a few left
他们还剩下几个项目的lambda项目
overs to take care of and those were
照顾照顾，那些是
handled under milling project corn as
在碾磨项目玉米下处理
well so the first of these changes we'll
好吧，我们首先进行这些更改
talk about is safe varargs on private
谈论私密的安全varargs
instance methods so back in jdk 5 or 6
实例方法回到jdk 5或6
you might have written code like this
您可能已经编写了这样的代码
you have a listed list of strings and
您有一个列出的字符串列表，
you want to initialize it using a razor
您想使用剃刀初始化它
as list one of the platform methods so
作为列出的平台方法之一
that should be fine so you have a
那应该很好，所以你有一个
genuine february in english and italian
真正的英语和意大利语二月
here so then if you did a compilation of
因此，如果您对
this you get a warning like this warning
这个你会得到像这样的警告
uncheck generic array creation from bar
从栏中取消选中通用数组创建
X parameter type list of string array so
字符串数组的X参数类型列表
this message sounds a little a little
这条消息听起来有点
concerning what's going on here is
关于这里发生的事情是
basically a bad interaction between
基本上之间的不良互动
arrays and generics from the VAR args
VAR args中的数组和泛型
parameter of arrays ah des lists and the
数组ah des列表的参数和
language specification requires an a
语言规范需要一个
warning being issued in the situation
在这种情况下发出警告
because something called heat pollution
因为所谓的热污染
might be going on there might be a
可能会继续
misleading that the compiler can't prove
误导编译器无法证明
that things have the proper type so
事物的类型正确
while it's correct in the sense of you
虽然这对你来说是正确的
want to warn when this situation might
想在这种情况下警告
possibly occur nothing bad actually
可能实际上不会发生任何不良情况
happens in this case so this is a false
在这种情况下发生，所以这是错误的
positive in the errors uninformative so
积极的错误，没有信息，所以
we prefer not to have these false potted
我们不希望这些假盆栽
positive errors we don't have to so for
正因错误，我们不必如此
that reason we added this safe varargs
因此我们添加了这个安全的varargs
annotation back in JDK 7 and say for our
注释返回到JDK 7中，并为我们说
basically says compiler please trust me
基本上说编译器请相信我
I I will I'm swearing that nothing acts
我会发誓什么也没做
bad along those lines is happening in
这些方面的坏事正在发生
the bogs method so you don't have to
沼泽方法，所以您不必
issue the warning and we added this
发出警告，我们添加了这个
annotation to a number of the platform
批注到多个平台
methods including arrays out as list
列表中包含数组的方法
now this annotation there's a few things
现在这个注解有几件事
it removes various warnings from the
它从中删除各种警告
method declarations but more importantly
方法声明，但更重要的是
it removes warnings from the method call
它从方法调用中删除警告
sites that is all the uses of these
这些都是这些用途的网站
methods so users wouldn't get this
方法，这样用户就不会得到这个
uninformative warning message anymore
不再提供有用的警告消息
now because of the design of annotations
现在因为注释的设计
annotations are only inherited for
注释仅继承
classes not interfaces or methods that
类不是接口或方法
means we can only use the safe args
表示我们只能使用安全参数
annotation on methods that can't be
注释不能的方法
overridden so what are the kinds of
被覆盖了，那是什么样的
methods in Java that can't be overridden
Java中无法覆盖的方法
we can't override final methods we can't
我们无法覆盖最终方法
override static methods we can't
覆盖我们无法使用的静态方法
override constructors because from a
覆盖构造函数，因为从
certain point of view at say the VM
从某种角度说虚拟机
level a constructor is this a very
级别的构造函数这是一个非常
special static method it has the same
具有相同的特殊静态方法
kind of feel to it but there's a fourth
有种感觉，但有第四种
kind of method you can't override and
一种您无法覆盖的方法，
that is a private method and we forgot
那是私人方法，我们忘了
about those when we were doing project
关于那些我们在做项目时
cloning JDK 7 so in JDK 9 now we added
克隆JDK 7，所以现在在JDK 9中我们添加了
them this is the corresponding part of
他们这是对应的部分
the Java language specification and we
Java语言规范，我们
were just able to add of two words to
只能添加两个单词到
cover the language change here so this
在这里介绍语言变化
is a very small language change we'd
这是我们的很小的语言更改
like them under nice and simple like
喜欢他们在很好和简单的喜欢下
this because they're often much more
这是因为它们通常更多
complicated and surprise us but there
复杂而令我们惊讶的
were no surprises here next I'll talk
接下来我会毫不奇怪
about the affected final variables and
关于受影响的最终变量，以及
try with resources so as a reminder
尝试使用资源来提醒
you'll be familiar from using a jd7 rate
使用jd7费率会很熟悉
you got prior three sources so you have
您有之前的三个资料来源，所以您有
your resource are in a block and now you
您的资源处于阻塞状态，现在您
manage it and this is roughly equivalent
管理它，这大致等效
to this where the compiler inserts a try
为此，编译器将插入一个try
finally around your block and it makes
终于在你的街区附近，它使
sure that close gets called on your
确保关闭调用您的
resource if the resource is not null
资源，如果资源不为null
it's actually a bit more complicated
实际上有点复杂
this about exception handling so in
这是关于异常处理的
terms of full disclosure this is the
完全披露条款是
folder screw ring here which is a more
文件夹螺丝环，这是更多
involved but we don't have to worry
参与其中，但我们不必担心
about this the compiler takes care of it
关于这一点，编译器会照顾它
for us so what's the structure of the
对我们来说，这是什么结构
resources to be managed in JDK 7 the
JDK 7中要管理的资源
rule we ended up with was you had to
规则，最后我们是你不得不
declare a fresh resource variable for
声明一个新的资源变量
the resources managed by the fire
大火管理的资源
resources statement that wasn't the
资源声明不是
original proposal originally you could
最初的建议你可以
pass in any expression that had the
传递具有
right type inside being Auto closeable
正确的类型，内部可自动关闭
meaning that the object in question had
表示该对象具有
a closed method but we found a problem
一个封闭的方法，但我们发现了一个问题
with that so let's say we have a
因此，假设我们有一个
resource R and then we manage our with
资源R，然后我们用
the chars resources statement and within
chars资源声明以及
the block of the tribe's resources agent
部落资源代理的障碍
we make our point to a different object
我们将观点指向另一个对象
so what should happen now when we get to
所以当我们到达
the end of the block which object should
块的末尾，哪个对象应该
have it's closed method be called should
是否应该调用它的关闭方法
it be resource one should it be
它应该是一种资源
resourced two should be both of them we
资源丰富的两个应该都是他们
decided we preferred not to solve this
决定我们不想解决这个问题
problem and the way we didn't solve it
问题和我们没有解决的方法
was to not allow you to just pass in an
就是不允许你只传递
arbitrary expression you have had a
你有一个任意表达式
fresh variable that had to be final so
必须是最终变量的新变量
that was a little so that that worked
那有点使它起作用
but it's a little annoying to have to
但这有点烦人
declare a fresh resource variable
声明一个新的资源变量
because there's some times when we know
因为有时候我们知道
this situation can't occur you can't
这种情况不可能发生，你不能
reassign the variable if it's final and
重新分配变量（如果是最终变量），
you can't reassign it if it's
如果是，则无法重新分配
effectively final effectively final
有效地最终有效地
means you could declare final and you
表示您可以宣布最终决定，而您
just haven't gotten around doing that
只是没有绕过这样做
yet so what we do now in in jdk 9 is we
但是，我们现在在jdk 9中所做的是
allow you to use an existing variable as
允许您将现有变量用作
long as it's a final effectively final
只要是最终有效的决赛
so instead of writing code like this
所以不要像这样写代码
here where we have to have this second
在这里，我们必须有第二个
resource just to manage our resources
资源只是为了管理我们的资源
statement we can just pass the final
声明我们可以通过最后
variable R right in there and this works
变量R就在那里，这可行
fine we avoid that problem of not
很好，我们避免了不
knowing which show
知道哪个节目
object to call clothes on it this wasn't
反对称呼衣服不是
too hard to do with a grammar level we
语法水平太难了
just expand the grammar a little bit to
只是将语法扩展到
allow variable access and the
允许变量访问和
specification change corresponding need
规格变更对应需求
is here now you might initially think
现在在这里，您可能最初会认为
that this would be very small spec
这将是非常小的规格
change is a sentence or two or a few
变化是一两个或几个句子
words because maybe you just want to
的话，因为也许你只是想
call allow say a local variable that's
打电话给允许说一个局部变量
fine or effectively final but we don't
很好或最终有效，但我们不
want to allow just local variable that's
只想允许本地变量
final effectively final we want more
最终有效，最终我们想要更多
orthogonality between the features so
特征之间的正交性
even if you have something like a final
即使你有一个像决赛的东西
field of a new object for an anonymous
匿名对象的新对象的字段
class that should be allowable too and
也应该允许的课程
that's what this change allows so
这就是该更改所允许的
diamond with anonymous classes so
带有匿名类的钻石
diamonds are formed under the earth at
钻石在地下形成
great depth and pressure and we'll have
巨大的深度和压力，我们将拥有
to go a little bit down the rabbit hole
往兔子洞下一点
to see what's going on here but
看看这里发生了什么，但是
hopefully worth the trip so I'll be
希望这次旅行值得，所以我会
using this example of a box type for the
使用此框类型示例
next few slides you can think of a box
接下来的几张幻灯片，您会想到一个盒子
is a simplified collection so it's a
是一个简化的集合，所以它是一个
parameterised type you can put object in
您可以将对象放入的参数化类型
and get objects out and so we have an
拿出物体，所以我们有一个
example here we have list of question
这里的例子我们有问题清单
mark that's a wildcard type and let's
标记为通配符类型，然后
say we want to put that into our box and
说我们想把它放进我们的盒子里，
using diamond so so that's fine now what
使用钻石，所以现在很好
the compiler has to do at this point is
编译器此时要做的是
infer what goes between the angle
推断角度之间的关系
brackets so Java is still a statically
方括号，因此Java仍然是静态的
typed language even if it's not
输入语言，即使不是
explicitly typed what that means is if
明确键入这是什么意思
we have programmers don't put in the
我们有程序员不投入
types for the angle brackets of the pram
婴儿车尖括号的类型
drive types the compiler has to do that
编译器必须执行的驱动器类型
work on our behalf instead in the
代替我们代表
process that that done by which that's
处理那完成的
done is called pipe inference so inside
完成称为管道推断，因此在内部
the compiler works what happens is it
编译器的工作原理是什么
infers this type list of capture of
推断此类型的捕获列表
question mark well this sounds a little
问号好，听起来有点
little unfamiliar so what what's going
有点不熟悉，怎么回事
on here is that this is something called
这是所谓的
a nan de notable type this is not a type
难辨的类型，这不是类型
we could write ourselves in the program
我们可以在程序中写自己
however it is a type available inside
但是它是内部可用的类型
the compiler this is actually a fairly
编译器这实际上是一个相当
common implementation technique for
常用的实现技术
compilers where there's a richer type
类型丰富的编译器
system in
系统中
by the compiler then is directly
然后由编译器直接
available to programmers so capture
可供程序员使用，因此可以捕获
conversion this is a type operation and
转换这是一个类型操作，
basically it means inside the compiler
基本上，这意味着在编译器内部
each of the wildcard Jesus question
每个通配符耶稣问题
marks which means there exist some type
标记，表示存在某种类型
is replaced by a new fresh type variable
替换为新的新鲜类型变量
inside the compiler some particular type
在编译器内部某些特定类型
variable so it's converted from a
变量，以便将其从
wildcard captured given a particular
给定一个特定的通配符
name this is described in the JLS and if
名称，这在JLS中进行了说明，如果
you're interested in the sort of thing
你对那种事情感兴趣
if you're reading this part of the Java
如果您正在阅读Java的这一部分
language specification it's good to have
语言规范，很好
a type theory manual in your body now
您体内的类型理论手册
box disease class it can be subclassed
箱病类可以细分
including being subclass anonymously
包括匿名子类化
again we want our features to to
再次，我们希望我们的功能
interact and be orthogonal but this
相互作用并正交，但这
anonymous sub classing is a bit of a
匿名子分类有点
problem for diamond as we'll see the
钻石的问题，我们将看到
next slide or two so let's say we wanted
下一张或两张幻灯片，假设我们要
to compile this anonymous subclass how
编译这个匿名子类
would that look so it's a class so it
那看起来像是一堂课吗
needs a class file so we'd have a name
需要一个班级文件，所以我们要有一个名字
somewhere light box dollar one and as a
一个灯箱美元的地方，作为一个
class file it has to be translated into
类文件，必须将其翻译成
a class file with the full set of
带有全套文件的类文件
attributes so in particular the generic
属性，因此特别是通用
information about a class is put into a
有关类的信息被放入
signature attribute in a class file the
类文件中的签名属性
signature attribute only can hold de
签名属性只能保留de
notable types the grammar for signatures
值得注意的类型签名的语法
doesn't allow non de notable types so
不允许非限定类型，所以
the grammar does not allow for lists of
语法不允许列出
captures question mark in particular so
尤其是捕获问号
this was rather unfortunate when we
当我们这很不幸
realized this in JDK 7 because this is
在JDK 7中意识到了这一点，因为这是
now a problem we can't and can't write
现在是一个我们不能写的问题
out a class file that has the
出一个具有
information needed so what's happened to
需要信息，所以发生了什么事
your well we've had language
你好，我们有语言
interactions over time way back when in
随着时间的流逝互动
turn class is routed in jdk 1.1 generics
turn类在jdk 1.1泛型中路由
were added in jdk 5 and generics and
在jdk 5和泛型中添加了
inner classes interoperate just fine we
内部类互操作就好了
made sure that occurred then in JDK 7
确保在JDK 7中发生了这种情况
diamond was at it so pair wise diamond
钻石就这样一对明智的钻石
in turn classes work just fine in pair
反过来，两人上课也很好
wise diamond in generics work just fine
仿制药中的明智钻石效果很好
after all that's what we're trying to do
毕竟这就是我们想要做的
but if we combine diamond inner classes
但是如果我们结合钻石内部类
in generics we have a visit from bag
在仿制药中，我们从袋子里来了
this is Duke's evil twin brother who's
这是杜克的邪恶双胞胎兄弟
looking to deface coin with our battery
希望用我们的电池破坏硬币
acid here
这里酸
so this is the case of today's problems
所以这就是今天的问题
coming from yesterday's solutions as our
来自昨天的解决方案
language architect Brian gets like the
语言架构师Brian变得像
second so as a result of when we found
因此，当我们发现
this in the JDK 7 we had to have a quick
在JDK 7中，我们必须快速
solution and we decide just to not allow
解决方案，我们决定只是不允许
diamond with anonymous classes at all we
我们都拥有匿名类的钻石
thought that was a little unfortunate
认为这有点不幸
and when we were finishing up the jsr we
当我们完成jsr时，
did know that it's feasible that future
确实知道未来是可行的
platforms we could allow use of diamonds
我们可以允许使用钻石的平台
when creating anonymous inner classes as
在创建匿名内部类时
long as the inferred type was a notable
只要推断的类型很明显
basically as long as that bad case that
基本上只要那个坏情况
can happen there's no reason we couldn't
可能发生，没有理由我们不能
use diamond and that is indeed what
用钻石，那的确是
we've done now in a Java 9 to allow dye
我们现在已经在Java 9中完成了允许染色
move anonymous classes as long as the
只要匿名类移动匿名类
inference works out fine this is the
推断很好，这是
spec spec text needed to do that it's a
规格文本需要做的是
little involved but luckily we have the
很少参与，但幸运的是我们有
spec guys to do that for us diamond in
专门为我们做钻石的家伙
JDK 7 by our experience is quite
根据我们的经验，JDK 7相当
effective
有效
it was able to get rid about 90% of the
它能够摆脱约90％的
explicit type arguments of constructor
构造函数的显式类型参数
call sites and we think with diamondden
呼叫站点，我们认为与Diamondden
anonymous classes in mine we can get rid
我的匿名类可以摆脱
of much of the remaining 10% we've had
我们剩下的10％中的大部分
good experiences updating jake oak jdk
更新杰克·奥克·杰克的好经验
code base to use this in particular
专门用于此的代码库
these calls to privilege action next up
接下来是对特权行动的呼吁
is underscore no longer an identifier
下划线不再是标识符
name this has been changed unfolding
名字这个已经改变了
over a number of years and releases part
多年来，并发布了一部分
of project lament in JDK 8 was not
JDK 8中的项目哀叹不是
allowing a single underscore to be used
允许使用单个下划线
as the parameter aim for lambda this was
作为lambda的参数目标是
to avoid confusion with the wunderbar
避免与Wunderbar混淆
feature of other languages you might
您可能会使用其他语言的功能
have used and while in JDK 8 it remained
已经使用过，而在JDK 8中，它仍然存在
legal to use a single underscore as a
将单个下划线用作
name in other context you do get this
在其他情况下命名
warning from Java C letting you know
Java C发出的警告通知您
that this might be going away and indeed
这可能会消失，的确
now and 9 it has gone away so why would
现在和9它已经消失了，为什么会
we do this this is against our usual
我们这样做是违反我们通常的
compatibility policy of you know keeping
您知道的兼容性政策
the programs that compile today
今天编译的程序
compiling tomorrow we want to reclaim an
明天编译，我们要回收
underscore for a single on the score for
在分数上下划线
some other purposes going forward there
还有其他目的
are a few potentials there may be a
有一些潜在的可能
partial diamond if you're partial
如果您偏爱钻石
witness or a official way to say I don't
证人或官方方式说我不
care or variable not used
不使用护理或变量
to get rid of them and some more
摆脱它们等等
particular uses are being discussed
特殊用途正在讨论中
under one of the Jets for upcoming JK's
在即将到来的JK的喷气机下
under a JEP three or two part of a more
在JEP的三分之二以下
lamda leftovers work next private on
lamda剩菜剩饭在下私人工作
interface methods again these are one
界面方法又是这些
another one of the project lambda
另一个lambda项目
cleanups project lambda added default
清理项目lambda添加了默认值
methods to interfaces that is methods
接口的方法即方法
that can have bodies so they're non
可以有身体，所以他们不是
abstract now at the VM level it was
现在在VM级别上抽象
convenient and necessary to have private
方便和有私人需要
methods in interfaces to help implement
接口中帮助实现的方法
these however private methods and
这些但是私人的方法和
interfaces were not valid at the source
接口在源端无效
level in JDK 8 so now we've changed that
JDK 8中的级别，所以现在我们已经更改了
in JDK 9 you can have both private
在JDK 9中，您可以同时拥有两个
instance methods as well as a private
实例方法以及私有方法
static method and why would you need
静态方法，为什么需要
these private methods in an interface
接口中的这​​些私有方法
you can have them as helper methods for
您可以将它们作为辅助方法
the other default methods so they're
其他默认方法，因此它们是
quite useful for that purpose next I'll
为此，我将非常有用
talk be talking about deprecation and
谈论被谈论过时和
imports this was one of another few
进口这是另外几个
small language changes so his background
语言变化很小，所以他的背景
a few years ago in the JDK say at the
几年前在JDK中说
start of JDK 8 we had some unpaid
从JDK 8开始，我们有一些未付费用
technical debt we had over 10,000
技术债务超过10,000
warnings of our own code from our own
来自我们自己的代码的警告
compiler so that wasn't a great
编译器，所以不是很好
situation to begin and over the years we
情况开始，这些年来我们
worked hard to not knock down those
努力不击倒那些
warnings so toward the start of jk9 we
警告，因此在JK9开始之前，我们
had about half as many about 5,000 in
有大约一半的约5,000
between the start of JDK 9 in about
在JDK 9开始之间
build 47 we went down from a few
47号楼，我们从几个落下
thousand warnings all the way to zero
一千个警告一直到零
we're quite happy about that we turned
我们对转身感到很高兴
on excellent W error in our build and
在我们的构建中出现极好的W错误
discovered our open code close code and
发现了我们的开放代码关闭代码并
all the other code in certain parts of
的某些部分中的所有其他代码
the platform now if you look at our
现在看一下平台
might files today this isn't quite true
可能今天提交了，这不是很正确
anymore there's still a few dozen it was
仍然有几十个
true for some time it was true for many
在一段时间内是正确的，在许多情况下是正确的
builds but we currently have a few dozen
构建，但我们目前有几十个
warnings remaining of a new and nine
新的和九个的剩余警告
category so we haven't quite gotten
类别，所以我们还没有完全了解
around to fixing those yet but maybe
围绕修复那些，但也许
after the conference I'll be able to fix
会议结束后我将可以修复
those in 9 and those warning free you're
那些9中的人和那些没有警告的人
mostly warning free modules include the
大多数没有警告的模块包括
base module desktop in core things like
基本模块桌面在诸如
the compiler we didn't get around to
我们无法解决的编译器
covering
覆盖
other parts of the platform so people
平台的其他部分
often talk about technical debt I'd also
经常谈论技术债务，我也会
like to talk about technical dividends
喜欢谈论技术红利
there's some benefits of doing this
这样做有一些好处
since we have exterior warning we don't
因为我们有外部警告，所以我们没有
have to worry about forgetting to
不必担心忘记
declare so you a version UID there's an
声明，以便您使用版本UID，
equals hash code check from Java C to
等于从Java C到
make sure you're overriding one when you
确保当您覆盖一个
do the other there's possible security
做到其他可能的安全
benefits the go-to fail go to fail
受益于失败
security issue from a few years ago is
几年前的安全问题是
similar to having an unintended switch
类似于意外开关
on a fall through and that is one of the
在跌倒，这是其中之一
conditions checked by Java C errors and
Java C错误检查的条件，以及
in that diagram the very low lowest
在那个图中最低的最低
bottom level was about deprecation so is
底层是关于弃用的
it really acceptable to have deprecated
弃用的确是可以接受的
items and I've written up some advice if
项目，我写了一些建议，如果
you want to try to remove the Java C
您想要尝试删除Java C
errors from your own code base so
来自您自己的代码库的错误，因此
deprecation errors we had hundreds of
弃用错误，我们有数百个
them there are a few ways you can
他们有几种方法可以
resolve them you can remove use of the
解决它们，您可以删除使用
deprecated element that's preferable in
不推荐使用的元素
some ways but you can't always do it you
有些方法，但您不能总是做到这一点
might need to keep how exposing that
可能需要保持如何曝光
functionality for your clients you can
您的客户的功能，您可以
propagate the deprecated annotation to
将不推荐使用的注释传播到
the youth site now in some in some ways
现在以某种方式在青年站点
the cure is worse than the disease right
治愈比疾病还差
because you're expanding rather than
因为你在扩张而不是
contracting the amount the amount of
签约金额
code that's deprecated so the last thing
不推荐使用的代码，所以最后一件事
you can do is you can use the suppress
你可以做的就是可以使用抑制
warnings annotation to declare that yes
警告注释声明是
I know I'm doing it but don't worry
我知道我在做，但是不用担心
about it it's okay so let's see how you
没关系，让我们看看你如何
might use that you have your client code
可能会使用您的客户代码
you have your deprecated library so when
您拥有已弃用的库，所以当
you compile you get this warning say
你编译你得到这个警告说
fine I can't I don't want to make this
好吧，我不能，我不想做这个
deprecated yourself like you have to
弃用自己，就像你必须
keep using deprecated libraries so
继续使用已弃用的库，因此
you'll just apply the suppress warnings
您只需应用抑制警告
annotation like so right at the top of
像这样在顶部的注释
the class that looks good so then you
看起来不错的课程，所以你
compile again and you still get a
再次编译，您仍然会得到一个
deprecation warning so what's going on
弃用警告，这是怎么回事
here well if you look a little more
好吧，如果你再看一点
closely what's going on you're actually
到底发生了什么事，你实际上
getting a warning in this case from the
在这种情况下，会从
import statement because you're
导入声明，因为您
importing a deprecated library this
导入不推荐使用的库
warning is mandated by the JLS now you
现在，您必须由JLS发出警告
might say well that's not a problem I'll
可能会说那不是我要解决的问题
just apply another suppress warnings
只是应用另一个抑制警告
annotation on the import statement you
您在导入语句上的注释
can't put the annotation now it's not
现在不能放注释了
syntactically valid
句法上有效
so this morning it's well-intentioned
所以今天早上好用
but it is kind of unhelpful because if
但这是无济于事的，因为如果
you can suppress all the other uses of
您可以禁止使用其他所有用途
the deprecated type why can why do you
过时的类型为什么可以为什么你
get this warning from the import
从导入中获得此警告
statement and you shouldn't have to do
声明，您不必做
something like change to using a fully
像更改为完全使用
qualified name everywhere to get a
到处都有合格的名称
warning free program @w a little silly
免费警告程序@wa little silly
so we change the language specification
所以我们改变语言规范
in 9 to not require a warning in this
在9中不需要警告
situation and with that it's now
情况，现在
tractable to clear a large code base of
易于处理以清除大量代码
deprecation warnings and the existence
弃用警告和存在
proof for that is the jdk code base it's
证明就是它的jdk代码库
off so there's a more changes to
关闭，因此还有更多更改
deprecation in jdk 9
在JDK 9中弃用
what does deprecation mean it's been
弃用是什么意思
around for a long time does it mean it's
周围很长一段时间，这意味着
harmful does it mean it's going away and
有害，这意味着它会消失，
if it does mean it's going away why
如果确实意味着它会消失，为什么
haven't you jetty cake guys removed
你不是把码头蛋糕的家伙都搬走了吗
anything or just remove one or two
任何东西或只是删除一两个
things after all these years well we
这些年来一切都好，我们
needed a richer set of tools to help
需要一套更丰富的工具来帮助
manage this and we did that by changing
管理这一点，我们通过更改来做到这一点
the deprecation annotation in JDK 9 to
JDK 9中的弃用注释
have more information in particular we
特别是有更多信息
added a method that says for removal
添加了一种表示删除的方法
that's boolean whether your appliance
无论您的设备是布尔型
removed or not and what this means to
是否删除，这意味着什么
the types we've applied it on in Java
我们在Java中应用的类型
Sea on the JDK if something is
如果有问题，请在JDK上进行操作
deprecated for removal true we intend to
不建议移除，我们打算
remove that item in the next major
在下一个专业中删除该项目
version other release so the items that
版本其他版本，以便该项目
are deprecated for removal true in JDK 9
在JDK 9中不建议删除true
we plan to remove in JDK 10 now there's
我们计划在JDK 10中删除
a new lint category for this removal the
此移除的新皮棉类别
category haven't quite finished cleaning
类别尚未完成清洁
up yet in our own code base so that
在我们自己的代码库中
there's an extra warning if you're using
如果您使用的是一个额外的警告
a for removal true item as opposed to
一个用于删除真实项目而不是
just a normal deprecated about them
只是对他们不赞成
there are updates for this throughout
整个都有更新
the platform from the language spec java
Java语言规范中的平台
c and java stock there's also a new
C和Java股票还有一个新的
static analysis to add a deborah's can
静态分析以添加deborah的罐头
that will analyze your class files and
它将分析您的班级文件，并
jar files and let you know when you're
jar文件，让您知道何时
using deprecated API s and deprecated
使用不推荐使用的API和不推荐使用的API
for removal api's so you can clean that
去除API的，所以你可以清理
up on your own without recompiling
自行完成，无需重新编译
finally I'll give a brief overview of
最后，我将简要概述
some of the library updates that went on
一些正在进行的库更新
in the release first there's a new
在发行版中首先有一个新的
versions string scheme base
版本字符串方案库
for many years we've had 1.5 1.6 1.7 1.8
多年来我们有1.5 1.6 1.7 1.8
you'll notice the one dots never
你会发现一个点永远不会
changing so we decided since it's not
变化，所以我们决定，因为它不是
changing it's no reason to have around
改变没有理由
so we dropped it so now the version from
所以我们删除了它，现在从
JT 9 will be something like not instead
JT 9将会像不是
there is a some entering work done with
有一些完成的工作
strings in JDK 9 there's a new internal
JDK 9中的字符串有一个新的内部
representation for compact strings they
紧凑字符串的表示形式
use a byte array instead of a car array
使用字节数组而不是汽车数组
so they're often denser so better memory
所以它们通常更密集，记忆更好
usage like garbage collection and the
垃圾收集和
like there's also a separate effort to
就像还有另外的努力
provide a communication channel
提供沟通渠道
interface between a Java compiler in the
Java编译器之间的接口
VM to have better string concatenation
VM具有更好的字符串连接
the shapes of string concatenation a
字符串串联的形状
Java compiler emits and the shapes that
Java编译器发出的形状
a particular VM can make go run fast
特定的VM可以使运行迅速
kind of change over time and this is a
随着时间的推移而改变，这是一个
stable point that can be used to get
可以用来获得的稳定点
better performance on that common
更好的表现
operation a few a few notes on
操作上的一些注意事项
collections so how many times have a
集合有多少次
written code like this you want to have
你想要的这样的书面代码
set of strings it's on modifiable so
这是一组可修改的字符串
you'll you'll get a hash there you'll
你会得到一个哈希，你会
put a few things into it and then put in
放一些东西然后放
wrapper this is kind of taking up a lot
包装器这是一种占用很多
of space for what it is so we might do
空间的大小，以便我们做
something like this instead we use a
像这样的东西，我们使用
raised dot as list and then we have the
凸起的点作为列表，然后我们有
wrapper there it's shorter but it's
那里的包装纸较短，但是
still kind of long there are other
还是有点长，还有其他
coding techniques you can use the double
可以使用双重编码技术
brace trick with the anonymous class I
用匿名类我做大括号
don't even show that but this is still
甚至不表明这一点，但这仍然
rather rather clunky for a very common
相当笨拙，非常常见
operation
运作
so in JDK 9 we don't have to write code
因此在JDK 9中，我们不必编写代码
like this anymore we can just write code
这样我们就可以编写代码了
like this which is much nicer these
这样更好的这些
there's a static factory methods of
有一个静态的工厂方法
added to list set and map these return
添加到列表集中并映射这些返回
unmodifiable collections maps and lists
不可修改的收藏地图和列表
have randomized iteration order in my
在我的中有随机的迭代顺序
colleagues two remarks worked on this
同事对此有两点评论
feature we'll be talking about this and
我们将要讨论的功能
other collection changes in jt9 later
稍后在jt9中进行其他集合更改
this afternoon delvia objects is a type
今天下午，delvia对象是一种类型
that has various utility methods we
有各种实用方法
expanded that as well to have some
也扩大了它以拥有一些
additional options for checking for null
用于检查null的其他选项
and checking for indices very common
并检查索引很常见
did math as I am we had a few changes
像我一样做数学，我们做了一些改变
there as well use multiply add which is
还有使用乘法加法
a hardware instruction for
硬件说明
floating-point that's getting more and
浮点数越来越多
more common if you do things like
如果您做类似的事情更常见
lexicographic array comparisons we now
我们现在的字典顺序比较
have intrinsic support so we can use
有内在的支持，所以我们可以使用
hardware instructions to make that go
硬件说明
faster on platforms with that approach
使用这种方法在平台上更快
also changes in concurrency and var
并发和变量也发生变化
handle for more advanced programming a
用于更高级编程的句柄
lot lots of other changes too that was
还有很多其他变化
just a few highlights so in summary in
重点介绍一下
jdk 9 we're making fundamental changes
jdk 9我们正在做出根本性的改变
to the program platform with modularity
模块化的程序平台
but we have many other changes as well
但是我们还有很多其他变化
and modularity and the other changes are
和模块化，其他变化是
geared toward encouraging the long term
着眼于长期鼓励
evolution of the platform so dhoop here
平台的发展如此发展
in the US is of legal drinking age Java
在美国是合法的饮酒年龄
has been around for over 21 years and we
已经存在超过21年了，我们
want a Java to be around for for many
希望有很多人可以使用Java
more decades to come after this some of
在这之后的几十年中
these language changes and other changes
这些语言更改和其他更改
are planned and unfold over multiple
已计划并展开多个
years and multiple ESA's and we have
年和多个ESA，我们拥有
better tooling now to help manage that
现在更好的工具来帮助管理
transition both for ourselves and for
为自己和自己过渡
Java users this is being done in open
Java用户这是公开进行的
JDK so if you want to get more involved
JDK，因此，如果您想更多地参与进来
you you're welcome to follow there and
您，欢迎您跟随那里，
those early access builds are available
这些早期访问版本可用
today for your evaluation so so please
今天为您评估，所以请
try out the jk9 early access to it early
尽早试用jk9
access bits this is a URL to the slides
访问位，这是幻灯片的URL
here we have time for some questions now
现在我们有时间来问一些问题
and you can also tweet questions the
您也可以在推特上提问
hashtag on the final slide thank you
最后一张幻灯片上的主题标签谢谢
if you have a question please come up to
如果您有任何疑问，请提出
one of the microphones in the aisles
过道中的麦克风之一
my question is them did you consider
我的问题是您是否考虑过
array slicing in 4/9 and would you
4/9中的数组切片，你会
consider in the future array slicing
在将来考虑数组切片
could could you say what you mean by
你能说出你的意思吗
that
那
like in Python where you can just slice
就像在Python中一样
up an array by using syntax of the
通过使用
language yeah the question was do we
语言是的，问题是我们
consider array slicing that that was not
考虑不是这样的数组切片
considered there are more array based
考虑有更多基于数组的
changes coming but I don't think that
改变来了，但我不认为
one is one being discussed I'll be down
一个正在讨论的一个我会失望的
here if there are other questions thank
这里如果还有其他问题谢谢
you for coming here today
你今天要来这里
[Music]
[音乐]